<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Made</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="tvshow">Tv Show</string>

    <string-array name="film_name">
        <item>1. Iron Man (2008)</item>
        <item>2. The Incredible Hulk (2008)</item>
        <item>3. Iron Man 2 (2010)</item>
        <item>4. Thor (2011)</item>
        <item>5. Captain America: The First Avenger (2012)</item>
        <item>6. The Avengers (2012)</item>
        <item>7. Iron Man 3 (2013)</item>
        <item>8. Thor: The Dark World (2013)</item>
        <item>9. Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014)</item>
        <item>10. Guardians of the Galaxy (2014)</item>
        <item>11. Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015)</item>
        <item>12. Ant-Man (2015)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_desc">
        <item>Tony Stark, a genius billionaire played by actor Robert Downey Jr.,
            owns the largest technology company, Stark Industries.
            Tony and his colleagues went to Afghanistan to conduct a demonstration of sophisticated weapons creation
            Stark Industries.
            He was later kidnapped by a group of rebels and forced him to make a deadly weapon.
            With his intelligence,
            he made a suit of armor to escape from prison and later became Iron Man.
        </item>
        <item>
            A scientist named Bruce Banner lives on the run, far from normal life and women who are
            he loved,Betty Ross. He looked for ways to cure gamma radiation that poisoned cells in his body and released
            great strength in him.
            Bruce was chased by his great enemy General Thunderbolt Ross, Betty Ross\'s father,
            to use his power as a military weapon.
            In addition, a new enemy named The Abomination with destructive power that exceeds the Hulk
            become the latest threat
        </item>
        <item>Connecting the first Iron Man movie, this time the world knows Tony Stark is identity
            Iron Man with his strong armor. Under government pressure, Tony refused to submit
            Iron Man\'s clothes so that the information behind it is not spread in the wrong hands.
            Together with Pepper Potts and James Rhodes, Tony led a new alliance for
            facing a new powerful force, Vanko.
        </item>
        <item>One of Marvel\'s most popular superhero films, Thor, played by actor Chris Hemsworth
            tells the story of a child from
            the god Odin. Thor is a powerful god but, a proud soldier.
            He reignited an ancient war in his home, Asgard, because of his reckless conduct.
            As a result of these actions, he must bear the consequences and Odin drove him to earth.
        </item>
        <item>When the world is at war, Steve Rogers (Chris Evans), registers to enter the army
            the American military but, he was always rejected because of his small posture.
            Steve volunteered to take part in an experiment that turned him into a super soldier
            known as Captain America.
            He with Bucky Barnes (Sebastian Stan) and Peggy Carter (Hayley Atwell) fought against
            the HYDRA organization led by Red Skull....
        </item>
        <item>When superheroes unite against evil creates an action scene that has been eagerly awaited by
            his fans. In the film, here are the Marvel icon heroes: Iron Man, Incredible Hulk, Thor, Captain America,
            Black Widow and Hawkeye joined The Avengers.
            Unexpected enemies appear and can threaten the security and safety of the world. \n
            This made Nick Fury, leader of the S.H.I.E.L.D international peace guard organization,
            gathering heroes to save the world from the brink of disaster.
        </item>
        <item>
            Returning in his Iron Man armor, Stark, must fight an enemy who knows no bounds and
            must be faced with his personal world which is destroyed by the enemy. This made his courage
            tested.
            Stark must survive with his tools and rely on his ingenuity too, his instincts to be able to
            protect the people closest to him.
            Through his fight, he found several answers to questions that had haunted him
        </item>
        <item>This sequel to Thor tells the action of Thor who fought to save the earth and all the world from the shadow of the enemy
            which targets the entire universe.
            The ancient race led by Malekith returned to change the universe in darkness.
            Thor, Odin\'s son begins a dangerous journey that will reunite himself with Jane
            Foster (Natalie Portman)
            and sacrifice everything to save the whole world.
        </item>
        <item>After a big fight with the Avengers in New York, Steve Rogers stayed
            in Washington DC trying to adapt to modern life.
            An attack took place, making Captain America and Black Widow also Falcon\'s new colleagues,
            against the new threat that is Winter Soldier.
        </item>
        <item>A space adventurer named Peter Quill (Chris Pratt), finds himself as an object
            hunted by Ronan. He stole a mysterious ball that Ronan craves, the villain
            threaten the entire universe.\n
            While away from Ronan, Quill meets Rocket, Groot, Gamora, and Drax,
            4 different individuals who find it difficult to unite. He discovered the original power of the mysterious ball an
            its threat to the universe.
            Quill and his team must do their best to save the galaxy.
        </item>
        <item>Avengers again successfully brought the superheroes united in the face of enemies. This time, Iron Man,
            Captain America, Thor, The Incredible Hulk, Black Widow and Hawkeye must re-unite for the sake of balance
            the planet.
            With epic action and adventure, the Avengers must stop the emergence of the Ultron
            evil with his terrible plan.
        </item>
        <item>The Marvel movie, starring Paul Rudd and Michael Douglas, is the first installment of the superhero
            Ant-Man. \n
            With diminished capabilities and increased strength, an accomplished thief named Scott Lang must
            help his mentor, Dr. Hank Pym.
            They must protect the secrets behind Ant-Man\'s clothes from dangerous threats and theft
            will save the world.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_quotes">
        <item>“I am Iron Man.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“You know, I know a few techniques that could help you manage that anger effectively.”
            – Dr. Bruce Banner.
        </item>
        <item>“I told you. I don\’t want to join your super-secret boy band.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“Brother, however I have wronged you, whatever I have done that has led you to do this, I am truly sorry.
            But these people are innocent: taking their lives will gain you nothing. So take mine, and end this.” –
            Thor.
        </item>
        <item>Whatever happens tomorrow you must promise me one thing. That you will stay who you are. Not a perfect
            soldier, but a good man.
            ” – Dr. Abraham Erskine.
        </item>
        <item>“The Avengers. That’s what we call ourselves; we’re sort of like a team.
            ‘Earth’s Mightiest Heroes’ type thing.” – Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“Things are different now. I have to protect the one thing that I can’t live without. That’s you.
            ”– Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“I gave you my word, that I would return.” – Thor.</item>
        <item>“People are going to die. I can’t let that happen.” – Steve Rogers.</item>
        <item>“I have lived most of my life surrounded by my enemies. I would be grateful to die surrounded by my
            friends.
            ” – Gamora.
        </item>
        <item>“Humans are odd. They think order and chaos are somehow opposites and try to control what won’t be. But
            there is grace in their failings. I think you missed that.
            ” – Vision.
        </item>
        <item>“Wait I didn’t steal anything! I was returning something I stole!” – Scott Lang.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_img">
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/1.-Iron-Man-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/2.-The-Incredible-Hulk-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/3.-Iron-Man-2-2010.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/4.-Thor-2011.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/5.-Captain-America-The-First-Avengers-2012.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/6.-The-Avengers-20121.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/7.-Iron-Man-3-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/8.-Thor-The-Dark-World-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/9.-Captain-America-The-Winter-Soldier-2014.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/10.-Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-2014.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/11.-Avengers-Age-of-Ultron-2015.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/12.-Ant-Man-2015.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
