<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Made</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="tvshow">Tv Show</string>

    <string-array name="film_name">
        <item>1. Iron Man (2008)</item>
        <item>2. The Incredible Hulk (2008)</item>
        <item>3. Iron Man 2 (2010)</item>
        <item>4. Thor (2011)</item>
        <item>5. Captain America: The First Avenger (2012)</item>
        <item>6. The Avengers (2012)</item>
        <item>7. Iron Man 3 (2013)</item>
        <item>8. Thor: The Dark World (2013)</item>
        <item>9. Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014)</item>
        <item>10. Guardians of the Galaxy (2014)</item>
        <item>11. Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015)</item>
        <item>12. Ant-Man (2015)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tv_show">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Fairy Tails</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Iron Fist</item>
        <item>Naruto</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Doom Patriot</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>God</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Grey Anathom</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="img_tv_show">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="desc_tv_show">
        <item>When it first hit the screen I loved this show. Its rather bare knuckle,
            vigilante grittiness really broke the candy covered shell, that encases so many comic book heros.
            Sadly in spite of strong stories and mature characterizations for me this show slowly started a downward spiral,
            gradually exchanging its originality for mainstream complacency.
            What really ruined things, in my view, was the migration of the character from a kind of anti hero to a politician.
            As if this wasnt bad enough, a thread of brittle and downright tiresome, lecturing political correctness crept in too.
        </item>
        <item>
            Lucy is a 17 year old girl, who wants to be a full fledged mage.
            One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation.
            But Natsu isnt just any ordinary kid, hes a member of one of the worlds most infamous mage guilds Fairy Tail.
        </item>
        <item>
            After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is
            struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of
            super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen
            guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to
            discover he is not the only meta-human who was created in the wake of the accelerator
            explosion and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners
            with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few
            close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive,
            but it wont be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become The Flash.
        </item>
        <item>
            Season 2 furthers the transformation of Danny​, a character with a fish out of water
            coming of age story making his way in a harsh new world, battling to work out who he is.
            This season, Dann​y​ has promised that with Matt Murdock gone, he will step up and protect his city.
            ​But a sinister plot twist threatens his very identity ​and he must conquer his villains
            to protect the town and people he holds close to his heart.
        </item>
        <item>
            Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.
            The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his
            quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru.
            After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha,
            and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy,
            as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dragon Ball Z is a Japanese animated television series produced by Toei Animation.
            Dragon Ball Z is the sequel to the Dragon Ball anime and adapts the last 26 volumes
            of the original 42 volume Dragon Ball manga series created by Akira Toriyama
            The series Debut in 1988-1995 on Weekly Shounen Jump. Dragon Ball Z depicts the
            continuing adventures of Goku and his companions to defend against an assortment of
            villains which seek to destroy or rule the Earth.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Doom Patrols members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman
            abilities but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden,
            the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate
            the weirdest phenomena in existence and to protect Earth from what they find.
        </item>
        <item>
            Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin Sweet animated series featuring the
            adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois
            have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and
            taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town)
            and Chris (the middle kid, he s not very bright but has a passion for movies).
            The final member of the family is Brian a talking dog and much more than a pet,
            he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
        </item>
        <item>
            A dark, gothic tale about three nuns, each a generation apart, living in an isolated
            convent by the coast, and an unwelcome visitor who enters their lives and changes their world forever.
        </item>
        <item>
            Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM.
            Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime worlds greatest foes,
            a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon s
            story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to
            navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City,
            the spawning ground of the worlds most iconic villains? And what circumstances
            created them the larger than life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin,
            The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?
        </item>
        <item>
            Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.
        </item>
        <item>
            This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young
            girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off book CIA agent and tries to
            unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_desc">
        <item>Tony Stark, a genius billionaire played by actor Robert Downey Jr.,
            owns the largest technology company, Stark Industries.
            Tony and his colleagues went to Afghanistan to conduct a demonstration of sophisticated weapons creation
            Stark Industries.
            He was later kidnapped by a group of rebels and forced him to make a deadly weapon.
            With his intelligence,
            he made a suit of armor to escape from prison and later became Iron Man.
        </item>
        <item>
            A scientist named Bruce Banner lives on the run, far from normal life and women who are
            he loved,Betty Ross. He looked for ways to cure gamma radiation that poisoned cells in his body and released
            great strength in him.
            Bruce was chased by his great enemy General Thunderbolt Ross, Betty Ross\'s father,
            to use his power as a military weapon.
            In addition, a new enemy named The Abomination with destructive power that exceeds the Hulk
            become the latest threat
        </item>
        <item>Connecting the first Iron Man movie, this time the world knows Tony Stark is identity
            Iron Man with his strong armor. Under government pressure, Tony refused to submit
            Iron Man\'s clothes so that the information behind it is not spread in the wrong hands.
            Together with Pepper Potts and James Rhodes, Tony led a new alliance for
            facing a new powerful force, Vanko.
        </item>
        <item>One of Marvel\'s most popular superhero films, Thor, played by actor Chris Hemsworth
            tells the story of a child from
            the god Odin. Thor is a powerful god but, a proud soldier.
            He reignited an ancient war in his home, Asgard, because of his reckless conduct.
            As a result of these actions, he must bear the consequences and Odin drove him to earth.
        </item>
        <item>When the world is at war, Steve Rogers (Chris Evans), registers to enter the army
            the American military but, he was always rejected because of his small posture.
            Steve volunteered to take part in an experiment that turned him into a super soldier
            known as Captain America.
            He with Bucky Barnes (Sebastian Stan) and Peggy Carter (Hayley Atwell) fought against
            the HYDRA organization led by Red Skull....
        </item>
        <item>When superheroes unite against evil creates an action scene that has been eagerly awaited by
            his fans. In the film, here are the Marvel icon heroes: Iron Man, Incredible Hulk, Thor, Captain America,
            Black Widow and Hawkeye joined The Avengers.
            Unexpected enemies appear and can threaten the security and safety of the world. \n
            This made Nick Fury, leader of the S.H.I.E.L.D international peace guard organization,
            gathering heroes to save the world from the brink of disaster.
        </item>
        <item>
            Returning in his Iron Man armor, Stark, must fight an enemy who knows no bounds and
            must be faced with his personal world which is destroyed by the enemy. This made his courage
            tested.
            Stark must survive with his tools and rely on his ingenuity too, his instincts to be able to
            protect the people closest to him.
            Through his fight, he found several answers to questions that had haunted him
        </item>
        <item>This sequel to Thor tells the action of Thor who fought to save the earth and all the world from the shadow of the enemy
            which targets the entire universe.
            The ancient race led by Malekith returned to change the universe in darkness.
            Thor, Odin\'s son begins a dangerous journey that will reunite himself with Jane
            Foster (Natalie Portman)
            and sacrifice everything to save the whole world.
        </item>
        <item>After a big fight with the Avengers in New York, Steve Rogers stayed
            in Washington DC trying to adapt to modern life.
            An attack took place, making Captain America and Black Widow also Falcon\'s new colleagues,
            against the new threat that is Winter Soldier.
        </item>
        <item>A space adventurer named Peter Quill (Chris Pratt), finds himself as an object
            hunted by Ronan. He stole a mysterious ball that Ronan craves, the villain
            threaten the entire universe.\n
            While away from Ronan, Quill meets Rocket, Groot, Gamora, and Drax,
            4 different individuals who find it difficult to unite. He discovered the original power of the mysterious ball an
            its threat to the universe.
            Quill and his team must do their best to save the galaxy.
        </item>
        <item>Avengers again successfully brought the superheroes united in the face of enemies. This time, Iron Man,
            Captain America, Thor, The Incredible Hulk, Black Widow and Hawkeye must re-unite for the sake of balance
            the planet.
            With epic action and adventure, the Avengers must stop the emergence of the Ultron
            evil with his terrible plan.
        </item>
        <item>The Marvel movie, starring Paul Rudd and Michael Douglas, is the first installment of the superhero
            Ant-Man. \n
            With diminished capabilities and increased strength, an accomplished thief named Scott Lang must
            help his mentor, Dr. Hank Pym.
            They must protect the secrets behind Ant-Man\'s clothes from dangerous threats and theft
            will save the world.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_quotes">
        <item>“I am Iron Man.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“You know, I know a few techniques that could help you manage that anger effectively.”
            – Dr. Bruce Banner.
        </item>
        <item>“I told you. I don\’t want to join your super-secret boy band.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“Brother, however I have wronged you, whatever I have done that has led you to do this, I am truly sorry.
            But these people are innocent: taking their lives will gain you nothing. So take mine, and end this.” –
            Thor.
        </item>
        <item>Whatever happens tomorrow you must promise me one thing. That you will stay who you are. Not a perfect
            soldier, but a good man.
            ” – Dr. Abraham Erskine.
        </item>
        <item>“The Avengers. That’s what we call ourselves; we’re sort of like a team.
            ‘Earth’s Mightiest Heroes’ type thing.” – Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“Things are different now. I have to protect the one thing that I can’t live without. That’s you.
            ”– Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“I gave you my word, that I would return.” – Thor.</item>
        <item>“People are going to die. I can’t let that happen.” – Steve Rogers.</item>
        <item>“I have lived most of my life surrounded by my enemies. I would be grateful to die surrounded by my
            friends.
            ” – Gamora.
        </item>
        <item>“Humans are odd. They think order and chaos are somehow opposites and try to control what won’t be. But
            there is grace in their failings. I think you missed that.
            ” – Vision.
        </item>
        <item>“Wait I didn’t steal anything! I was returning something I stole!” – Scott Lang.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_img">
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/1.-Iron-Man-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/2.-The-Incredible-Hulk-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/3.-Iron-Man-2-2010.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/4.-Thor-2011.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/5.-Captain-America-The-First-Avengers-2012.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/6.-The-Avengers-20121.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/7.-Iron-Man-3-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/8.-Thor-The-Dark-World-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/9.-Captain-America-The-Winter-Soldier-2014.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/10.-Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-2014.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/11.-Avengers-Age-of-Ultron-2015.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/12.-Ant-Man-2015.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="quote">Quote</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
</resources>
