<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Made</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="tvshow">Tv Show</string>
    <string name="releaseDate">Release Date</string>

    <string-array name="film_name">
        <item>1. Iron Man (2008)</item>
        <item>2. The Incredible Hulk (2008)</item>
        <item>3. Iron Man 2 (2010)</item>
        <item>4. Thor (2011)</item>
        <item>5. Captain America: The First Avenger (2012)</item>
        <item>6. The Avengers (2012)</item>
        <item>7. Iron Man 3 (2013)</item>
        <item>8. Thor: The Dark World (2013)</item>
        <item>9. Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014)</item>
        <item>10. Guardians of the Galaxy (2014)</item>
        <item>11. Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015)</item>
        <item>12. Ant-Man (2015)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rilis_date">
        <item>April 1, 2019</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009</item>
        <item>October 7, 2014</item>
        <item>March 17, 2017</item>
        <item>February 15, 2007</item>
        <item>April 26, 1989</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>September 22, 2014</item>
        <item>March 27, 2005</item>
        <item>March 28, 2019</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tv_show">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Fairy Tails</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Iron Fist</item>
        <item>Naruto</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Doom Patriot</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>God</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Grey Anathom</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="img_tv_show">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="desc_tv_show">
        <item>When it first hit the screen I loved this show. Its rather bare knuckle,
            vigilante grittiness really broke the candy covered shell, that encases so many comic book heros.
            Sadly in spite of strong stories and mature characterizations for me this show slowly started a downward spiral,
            gradually exchanging its originality for mainstream complacency.
            What really ruined things, in my view, was the migration of the character from a kind of anti hero to a politician.
            As if this wasnt bad enough, a thread of brittle and downright tiresome, lecturing political correctness crept in too.
        </item>
        <item>
            Lucy is a 17 year old girl, who wants to be a full fledged mage.
            One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation.
            But Natsu isnt just any ordinary kid, hes a member of one of the worlds most infamous mage guilds Fairy Tail.
        </item>
        <item>
            After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is
            struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of
            super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen
            guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to
            discover he is not the only meta-human who was created in the wake of the accelerator
            explosion and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners
            with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few
            close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive,
            but it wont be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become The Flash.
        </item>
        <item>
            Season 2 furthers the transformation of Danny​, a character with a fish out of water
            coming of age story making his way in a harsh new world, battling to work out who he is.
            This season, Dann​y​ has promised that with Matt Murdock gone, he will step up and protect his city.
            ​But a sinister plot twist threatens his very identity ​and he must conquer his villains
            to protect the town and people he holds close to his heart.
        </item>
        <item>
            Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.
            The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his
            quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru.
            After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha,
            and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy,
            as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dragon Ball Z is a Japanese animated television series produced by Toei Animation.
            Dragon Ball Z is the sequel to the Dragon Ball anime and adapts the last 26 volumes
            of the original 42 volume Dragon Ball manga series created by Akira Toriyama
            The series Debut in 1988-1995 on Weekly Shounen Jump. Dragon Ball Z depicts the
            continuing adventures of Goku and his companions to defend against an assortment of
            villains which seek to destroy or rule the Earth.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Doom Patrols members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman
            abilities but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden,
            the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate
            the weirdest phenomena in existence and to protect Earth from what they find.
        </item>
        <item>
            Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin Sweet animated series featuring the
            adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois
            have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and
            taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town)
            and Chris (the middle kid, he s not very bright but has a passion for movies).
            The final member of the family is Brian a talking dog and much more than a pet,
            he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
        </item>
        <item>
            A dark, gothic tale about three nuns, each a generation apart, living in an isolated
            convent by the coast, and an unwelcome visitor who enters their lives and changes their world forever.
        </item>
        <item>
            Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM.
            Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime worlds greatest foes,
            a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon s
            story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to
            navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City,
            the spawning ground of the worlds most iconic villains? And what circumstances
            created them the larger than life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin,
            The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?
        </item>
        <item>
            Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.
        </item>
        <item>
            This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young
            girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off book CIA agent and tries to
            unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_desc">
        <item>
            Tony Stark, seorang miliarder jenius yang diperankan oleh aktor Robert Downey Jr,
            memiliki perusahaan teknologi terbesar, yaitu Stark Industries.\n
            Tony dan rekan kerjanya pergi ke Afghanistan untuk melakukan sebuah demonstrasi senjata canggih ciptaan
            Stark Industries.
            Ia kemudian diculik oleh sekelompok pemberontak dan memaksanya untuk membuat senjata mematikan.\n
            Dengan kecerdasannya,
            ia membuat sebuah baju armor untuk melarikan diri dari tahanan dan kemudian jadi Iron Man.
        </item>
        <item>
            Seorang ilmuwan bernama Bruce Banner hidup dalam pelarian, jauh dari kehidupan normal dan wanita yang
            dicintainya,
            Betty Ross. Ia mencari cara untuk menyembuhkan radiasi gamma yang meracuni sel dalam tubuhnya dan melepaskan
            kekuatan besar dalam dirinya.\n
            Bruce dikejar oleh musuh besarnya yaitu Jenderal Thunderbolt Ross, ayah Betty Ross,
            untuk memanfaatkan kekuatannya sebagai senjata militer.\n
            Di samping itu, musuh baru bernama The Abomination dengan kekuatan destruktif yang melebihi Hulk
            menjadi ancaman terbaru.
        </item>
        <item>
            Menyambung film Iron Man pertama, kali ini dunia mengetahui Tony Stark adalah identitas
            Iron Man dengan baju armor-nya yang kuat. Dibawah tekanan pemerintah, Tony menolak menyerahkan
            baju Iron Man agar informasi dibalik semua itu tidak tersebar di tangan yang salah.\n
            Bersama dengan Pepper Potts dan James Rhodes, Tony memimpin sebuah persekutuan baru untuk
            menghadapi kekuatan baru yang kuat yaitu, Vanko.
        </item>
        <item>
            Salah satu film superhero Marvel paling populer yaitu, Thor yang diperankan oleh aktor Chris Hemsworth
            bercerita tentang seorang anak dari
            dewa Odin. Thor adalah dewa yang kuat namun, seorang prajurit yang angkuh.\n
            Ia menyalakan kembali perang kuno di tempat tinggalnya, Asgard karena perbuatannya yang sembrono.
            Akibat perbuatannya tersebut, ia harus menanggung akibatnya dan Odin mengusirnya ke bumi.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ketika dunia sedang dalam masa perang, Steve Rogers (Chris Evans), mendaftar untuk masuk ke dalam pasukan
            militer Amerika tetapi, ia selalu di tolak karena postur tubuhnya yang kecil.\n
            Steve secara sukarela mengikuti sebuah eksperimen yang mengubahnya menjadi prajurit super yang
            dikenal sebagai Captain America.\n
            Ia bersama Bucky Barnes (Sebastian Stan) dan Peggy Carter (Hayley Atwell) berperang melawan
            organisasi HYDRA yang dipimpin oleh Red Skull.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ketika superheroes bersatu melawan kejahatan menciptakan sebuah adegan aksi yang sangat ditunggu-tunggu oleh
            penggemarnya. Di film, ini para hero ikon Marvel: Iron Man, Incredible Hulk, Thor, Captain America,
            Black Widow, dan Hawkeye bergabung dalam The Avengers.\n
            Musuh yang tak terduga muncul dan dapat mengancam keamanan dan keselamatan dunia.\n
            Hal ini membuat Nick Fury, pemimpin organisasi penjaga kedamaian internasional S.H.I.E.L.D,
            mengumpulkan para hero untuk menyelamatkan dunia dari ambang bencana.
        </item>
        <item>
            Kembali dengan baju armor Iron Man-nya, Stark, harus melawan musuh yang tidak mengenal batas dan
            harus diperhadapkan dengan dunia pribadinya yang dihancurkan oleh musuh. Hal ini membuat keberaniannya
            diuji.\n
            Stark harus bertahan dengan alat-alatnya dan mengandalkan kecerdikan juga, instingnya untuk dapat
            melindungi orang-orang terdekatnya.\n
            Lewat pertarungannya, ia menemukan beberapa jawaban dari pertanyaan yang telah menghantuinya sel
        </item>
        <item>
            Sekuel Thor ini menceritakan aksi Thor yang berjuang menyelamatkan bumi dan semua dunia dari bayangan musuh
            yang mengincar seluruh alam semesta.
            Ras kuno yang dipimpin oleh Malekith kembali untuk mengubah alam semesta dalam kegelapan.\n
            Thor, sang putra Odin memulai perjalanan berbahayanya yang akan menyatukan kembali dirinya dengan Jane
            Foster (Natalie Portman)
            dan mengorbankan segalanya untuk menyelamatkan seluruh dunia.
        </item>
        <item>
            Setelah pertarungan besar dengan para Avengers di New York, Steve Rogers tinggal
            di Washington DC mencoba untuk beradaptasi dengan kehidupan modern.\n
            Sebuah penyerangan terjadi, membuat sang Captain America dan Black Widow juga rekan baru Falcon,
            melawan ancaman baru yaitu Winter Soldier.
        </item>
        <item>
            Seorang petualang luar angkasa bernama Peter Quill (Chris Pratt), mendapati dirinya sebagai objek yang
            diburu oleh Ronan. Ia mencuri sebuah bola misterius yang sangat diidamkan Ronan, penjahat yang
            mengancam seluruh alam semesta.\n
            Ketika menyingkir dari Ronan, Quill bertemu dengan Rocket, Groot, Gamora, dan Drax,
            4 individu berbeda yang sulit bersatu. Ia menemukan kekuatan asli bola misterius tersebut dan
            ancamannya terhadap alam semesta.\n
            Quill dan timnya harus melakukan yang terbaik untuk menyelamatkan galaksi.
        </item>
        <item>
            Avengers kembali sukses membawa para superheroes bersatu dalam menghadapi musuh. Kali ini, Iron Man,
            Captain America, Thor, The Incredible Hulk, Black Widow dan Hawkeye harus kembali bersatu demi keseimbangan
            planet.
            Dengan aksi dan petualangan yang epik, para Avengers harus menghentikan kemunculan Ultron yang
            jahat dengan rencana mengerikannya.
        </item>
        <item>
            Film Marvel yang dibintangi oleh Paul Rudd dan Michael Douglas ini adalah sekuel pertama dari superhero
            Ant-Man.\n
            Dengan kemampuan mengecil dan kekuatan yang bertambah, seorang pencuri ulung bernama Scott Lang harus
            membantu mentornya, Dr. Hank Pym.\n
            Mereka harus melindungi rahasia dibalik baju Ant-Man dari ancaman-ancaman yang berbahaya dan pencurian yang
            akan menyelamatkan dunia. \n
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_quotes">
        <item>“I am Iron Man.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“You know, I know a few techniques that could help you manage that anger effectively.”
            – Dr. Bruce Banner.
        </item>
        <item>“I told you. I don’t want to join your super-secret boy band.” – Tony Stark.</item>
        <item>“Brother, however I have wronged you, whatever I have done that has led you to do this, I am truly sorry.
            But these people are innocent: taking their lives will gain you nothing. So take mine, and end this.” –
            Thor.
        </item>
        <item>Whatever happens tomorrow you must promise me one thing. That you will stay who you are. Not a perfect
            soldier, but a good man.
            ” – Dr. Abraham Erskine.
        </item>
        <item>“The Avengers. That’s what we call ourselves; we’re sort of like a team.
            ‘Earth’s Mightiest Heroes’ type thing.” – Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“Things are different now. I have to protect the one thing that I can’t live without. That’s you.
            ”– Tony Stark.
        </item>
        <item>“I gave you my word, that I would return.” – Thor.</item>
        <item>“People are going to die. I can’t let that happen.” – Steve Rogers.</item>
        <item>“I have lived most of my life surrounded by my enemies. I would be grateful to die surrounded by my
            friends.
            ” – Gamora.
        </item>
        <item>“Humans are odd. They think order and chaos are somehow opposites and try to control what won’t be. But
            there is grace in their failings. I think you missed that.
            ” – Vision.
        </item>
        <item>“Wait I didn’t steal anything! I was returning something I stole!” – Scott Lang.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_img">
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/1.-Iron-Man-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/2.-The-Incredible-Hulk-2008.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/3.-Iron-Man-2-2010.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/4.-Thor-2011.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/5.-Captain-America-The-First-Avengers-2012.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/6.-The-Avengers-20121.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/7.-Iron-Man-3-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/8.-Thor-The-Dark-World-2013.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/9.-Captain-America-The-Winter-Soldier-2014.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/10.-Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-2014.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/11.-Avengers-Age-of-Ultron-2015.jpg</item>
        <item>https://ecs7.tokopedia.net/blog-tokopedia-com/uploads/2019/01/12.-Ant-Man-2015.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="quote">Kutipan</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
</resources>
